wagist.com 2014-06-17

# DreamHost Privacy Policy | DreamHost

## Collected Information

When you sign up for service with DreamHost Web Hosting, we collect personal information from you including your name, e-mail address, billing address, security question (and answer), credit card or other payment information, social security number (in limited instances) and a password.

We may also collect the URL from which you linked into our site, your IP address, and your browser type and version.

We also, as a manner of course, collect information from you which is required to establish and maintain an account with us, some of which may be personally identifiable, depending on your needs and the needs of your hosted data.

## Use of Customer Information

Customer privacy is something we take very seriously at DreamHost. With the exception of trusted business affiliates and/or associates who work on behalf of or in connection with DreamHost, DreamHost will not provide or sell to any third party your personal information and will keep all such data confidential.

Customers may review and alter the contact information associated with their DreamHost account(s) at the following URL: <https://panel.dreamhost.com/id/index.cgi?tab=contact>.

DreamHost’s primary business operations are located in the state of California in the United States. As such, DreamHost is subject to obey the laws of this jurisdiction and may be called upon by various law enforcement agencies to comply with ongoing investigations. Compliance may include the secure handover of customer data to a legally-authorized government agency.

When permitted by law DreamHost will disclose to any customer that is the subject of a government investigation and any data requests pertaining to customers’ personally identifiable information and/or hosted data.

Changes to DreamHost’s privacy policy will be communicated to customers via DreamHost’s monthly customer newsletter. Customers who elect to opt-out of receiving this newsletter will not receive notifications of changes to the privacy policy. All changes, once posted publicly to dreamhost.com, shall take effect immediately across DreamHost’s entire customer base.

DreamHost may utilize third party platforms to provide web-based advertisements for DreamHost services after a user has visited and left DreamHost’s website. DreamHost and its advertising partners comply with “do not track” signals provided either by a user’s web browser automatically, or by a user manually opting-out at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

## Whois Privacy Services

Please note that the contact information that you provide to us is used to register your domain name and is, by the very nature of the domain registration system, available for public viewing in many places on the Internet via the use of the ‘whois’ tool.

Whois Privacy, which masks your whois contact information via proxy, as offered by DreamHost does not act as a shield from legal liability in conjunction with Domain Registration. In order to preserve neutrality in disputes between 3rd parties and domain registrants, DreamHost will act in accordance with ICANN Registrar Accreditation agreement section 3.7.7.3 upon receipt of actionable evidence of illegal activity. This means that identifying information will be provided to law enforcement and officials of the court including attorneys as situations require in order to preserve DreamHost’s neutrality in any litigation.

## Lucky Orange Web Analytics Service

This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange may record keystroke information that you voluntarily enter on this website. Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system. You can choose to disable the Lucky Orange Service at [http://www.luckyorange.com/disable.php.](http://www.luckyorange.com/disable.php) Note, that doing so will disable other features of the Lucky Orange system that this site employs such as 1-to-1 support chat.
